Hello friends, today we are going to talk about
Lombard General Insurance Company Limited's
stock market in the cross market.
1405 percent weighting tweet SMS is 3.0
percent positive thinking. If we talk about the
action chart pattern, then the company has
given a return of 106 percent till now.
If we talk about the last six months, then in the last six
months you have seen a decline in the company,
if we talk about the last month, then in the
last month you have
seen a return of up to 100 percent in the company. There is an
initial water for visit, along with that
financial difficulties, know how the quarterly results are
decreasing and how the future will be. If we talk about
hair dresser
shop, computers in it, if we
talk about the difference in the quarter of this year, then where the total profit of the company last year was Rs
38.54
crore, it increased to Rs 40.36 crore.
You got improvement in the bank way, where there was
three more centuries in the last quarter in the cutting and net profit scooter, that was Rs 312,
I told you that there is a slight decrease in the network.
If we talk about the
company's profit,
it was Rs 535 crore in the last quarter and you will also see it in other areas as well.
Talking about last year's quarter for which the
company's profit was Rs 389 crore, it
increased to Rs 640 crore. Here
you have seen an increase in revenue by 22%.
Then look at your revenue, it was Rs 300.45 crore,
whereas on Monday
you have seen an increase of up to 10% in the network. If we talk about the
company's profit, it will be
less than 1.5 crore from last year's quarter, it has
only failed. Here
you have seen a decrease in the company's profit.
If we talk about last year i.e.
financial year 2021 and clearly,
where the total profit of the company in financial year 2021 was Rs
12168 crore, it increased to Rs 16229
crore. You have seen an improvement in the revenue of the company. If we
look at the improvement of the profit, then
after this it increased to Rs 1478 crore.  12071 crore or the
needle has reduced by half the company's net profit
was Mohammad Rafi, we saw the guarantee council, this was the
responsibility of the company, it has reduced to 25.29
crore, you have seen a 20% decline in the
company's result, if we talk about our
rooms, quarters, Tonk Phatak, if you compare
religious waterproof with last year's quarter
and last year's
financial year 2010 financial, then you should
reduce it, friends, if you have seen a
decline in the company's network and other premises, then you know when and in
what way we have been doing it for the last few years so
that our work can be done in the future,
if we talk about the last few years, then
if we talk from 2017 to 2021, then
in 2017 this complete winners continued till 6778 crore, let's see
here it increased to
10743 crore in 2021, but when we talk
within 2030, you will see the company's
revenue and networking and if we
talk about the company's cricket, then
on net profit  Then here the company
's canteen, he studied from 2017 to 2021 seconds,
where in 2017
it increased to 700 crores on computer network,
whose is the second, fourth status in his clothes, here he has
doubled his network in the last 4 years,
but this year financial there and in this
you have seen a decline in the net profit of the company as
well, which is
just this much tiffin pack in the company purse,
similarly now you get to see the same chart pattern in 21 center,
if we talk in a research way, then in
2017 this GPS here was 15.1 crores, it increased to
2.41 crores by 2021, but
in 2022 you saw a decline in it
or if we talk about the
result in the balance sheet, then Jatak Mirza's 2017 Chandra
was 340 crores, that is continuously see Mar 2021
Cancer is increasing area from walnut company,
here he is involved in canter, but you will get information about the
financial year of the company
You saw a decline in the results of 2022, which is the
system of Quarter Final Series-2005 for investing in the company till the vision actresses of childhood, so
friends, it is going to be if the company
records its distribution network and if you
get it on train time, then you will get to
read it in the system, you may see a decline in the store
here in your own for the coming future,
you must have liked this video, supported
on